One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
Vergo and Joker!
The Beginning of Caesar's Masterplan!
A Certain Island in the New World
Marines!
Please listen to my request... Please find our children!
There was an incident three years ago when our children went missing.
Search just one more time, please!
Surely you can see that it's absurd to say that children playing in our neighborhood actually died at sea!
We just can't believe it!
Please! Search just one more time!
Re-open the investigation!
At least, please tell our story to Captain Tashigi!
We hear that she's a kind person who will listen to our story!
What a load of crap!
Are you trying to insult us?!
I'll have you know that we're G-5 marines too!
You say that you doubt the Navy's reports?
Are you trying to complain
about the way we handle this jurisdiction?!
You're complaining far too much!
That's not what...
This is pointless. Far too pointless!
Be reasonable! Far too reasonable!
Your children died at sea!
Commodore, you go far too far!
Navy G-5 Squadron 06
Commodore Yarisugi
Yarisugi: Going too far
We've confirmed this with the head of G-5, Vice-Admiral Vergo far too many times.
We've investigated it ten thousand times!
But...
If you keep on making a fuss about this,
then we'll charge you with obstruction of justice, massacre everyone, and torch the town!
Commodore, that's far too much.
Hmph, they want to talk to Tashigi-chan?
They're far too insolent!
Though, sometimes I wish
she was under my command.
That'd be far too marvelous!
Your imagination's far too wild!
Unfortunately, that girl's in Squadron 01.
She works closely with Vice-Admiral Smoker.
Far too closely!
We don't have time to reopen investigations for a three year old incident.
Our free time is far too limited!
Far too limited!
Damn turds.
You said too much!
Do you think they really
talked to the head, Vice-Admiral Vergo?
He really did save this island from pirates once.
He was a perfect gentleman. It's hard to imagine
that he's a member of a group of ruffians like G-5.
Did he really say that this was just a shipwreck?
They're alive!
They have to be alive!
They must be out there somewhere!
Punk Hazard
Ruins of Laboratory One and Two
Nami and Usopp's Group
My head's gonna split in two!
Usopp! Hurry up and knock 'em out!
I'm trying to! But each time it's less effective!
Take these chains off!
The withdrawal symptoms
must be too strong this time!
Then what're we going to do?
We have to find some way to hold them down.
I'm counting on you, Sanji!
I'm Nami!
Oh, I forgot.
Damn. You look so strong on the outside.
Well excuse me!
Misters!
Candy! Give us candy!
Candy! Candy!
My head hurts!
The pain!
Just give us some candy... it'll make it all better.
Candy.
Give us candy!
Here they come!
Hey! Hey! I can attack them now, right?!
They're monsters!
No!
Idiot! They're still kids!
But we can't avoid them forever!
It's Master!
Are you okay, children?
Now, let's go home. Back to the lab.
It's too dangerous out here.
Master!
Master?!
Central Lake
The Slime's getting angry!
Why now, all of a sudden?
Maybe it's because we blew up the mini-slimes?
Mayhaps they're like its children? But we had no choice.
Huh, it's changing shape!
What could it be becoming?
What is that, a frog?
Isn't it a lizard?
Run!
Is there no end to the mini-slimes it can create?
No, it appears that
the big one on the other shore is shrinking.
So, the big one will eventually disappear?
Or maybe it's getting smaller because it's launching itself over here piece by piece?
We're done for if something that size
starts rampaging over here.
Yeah! Cut it and it spews gas, burn it and it explodes.
And it'll be much much bigger.
The lab probably isn't even safe.
What?! Then we must make haste!
Momonosuke!
What're you two going to do? I'm heading for the lab.
Then we have to go there too, you idiot!
Who're you calling an idiot?
You're too unreliable!
If you get separated from Kin'emon, then you'll get lost.
Do you expect us to search
the whole damn island for you?!
Zoro-san, Sanji-san, this is no time for fighting...
I'd like to see his sword techniques as well...
Let's go to the lab!
Give us back Smokey, Caesar!
In Front of Caesar's Laboratory
Give us back Tashigi-chan!
What's with this huge shutter? We can't dent it.
Even a bazooka doesn't do anything.
Maybe there's a back door?
No good. These shutters are on every side.
That gas bastard!
You don't think that this is a trap, do you?
What are you saying? Don't be stupid.
Those creepy jellies aren't raining down anymore...
but if you pay attention,
you'll see they're merging and getting bigger.
There's no chance of stealing a ship anymore.
They're blocking our path.
And they took our Snail Phones,
so there's no way to contact anyone.
What should we do?!
What's Caesar trying to do?
Who knows? He doesn't tell me everything.
But since he's woken up his pet, Smiley, he might have an experiment in mind.
By the way, Vergo...
did you have a Hamburger for breakfast?
How did you know? I love them.
You've got some on the side of your face.
I'd really like to see this experiment.
Is everyone outside going to die?
Probably. It'll be safe in the lab, though.
Hey, Vergo!
The marines outside are from G-5.
They're your own men!
Are you planning to let them all die?
Yeah, that's about right.
What?!
But what a lovely collection of characters we have in this cage.
It's quite a sight.
Seeing the two of you in the same cage
really takes me back.
Oh yeah, you're right!
You captured me and Smoke-man back in Alabasta!
Shut the hell up.
Even at a time like this,
you don't care what's going on, do you?
Smoker-san, what do these feelings mean?
What should I do?
It seems your worst case scenario was right.
A member of G-5 would have to be
covering up the kidnappings by lying to the media.
That means that Caesar used Vergo
to change the kidnapping reports into shipwrecks.
In other words,
the corruption comes from the very top of G-5.
You could say that's characteristic of G-5,
but it's a disgrace to the entire Navy!
How could you do this?!
What, is he some kind of bad guy?
It certainly appears to be so.
You shouldn't feel bad for not realizing it.
It isn't like Vergo actually betrayed the Marines...
since he was really a pirate the entire time.
A pirate... What?!
That's right. Before he was famous,
he joined the Navy on Joker's orders.
He's slipped by unnoticed for fifteen years,
slowly gaining in rank.
Joker has no other Marine
more useful and trustworthy than him.
Vergo's been a member of Joker's crew
from the very start.
How could...
Joker... Wasn't that
the name of that broker from the underworld?
It's pathetic that I couldn't smell this rat.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
I prefer to think that the rat deserves admiration
when it evades the great White Hunter, Smoker-kun.
I had to be very careful
ever since you transferred in from HQ.
It feels good now that I don't have to worry
about you anymore.
And even if my true nature was revealed,
I have a plan to handle it.
You must know why
I'm not worried about telling you all this, don't you?
Vice-Admiral Smoker and Captain Tashigi...
I'm going to shut your mouths
by making sure that you die here.
Caesar will take care of my subordinates outside.
It must be done. This is important turf for Joker.
We cannot allow anyone to return alive
once they've figured out what's happening here.
As always,
we'll be able to make it look like an accident.
Vergo!
Hey, Traf. Who's this Joker?
I used to be part of his crew as well.
That's how I know Vergo.
Joker is merely his title as an underworld broker.
You already know him, quite well.
What are you talking about?
He's one of the seven world-famous pirates.
A member of the World Government sanctioned Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Donquixote Doflamingo.
Master!
So...
you're the one who kidnapped these kids?!
What's he doing here?
Did Luffy and the others go the wrong way?
You've done something terrible.
Terrible?
Why did you take them away?
Can't you see that the children are suffering?
What?!
Hey, don't be an idiot! Cut it out, Nami!
And whose fault is it that they're suffering?!
Stop it! Didn't Law say he was
a Logia user with a bounty of 300 million?
What drugs have you
been giving to these young children?
All of them really want to go home!
Their parents must be searching for them too!
We're definitely going to
take the children away from this place!
They don't look like they want to go home.
Master!
Hold on!
Hey, wait!
Don't go! You don't want
to go back to the laboratory, do you?!
Get out of my way!
Usopp!
That's right. Come on home, children.
Please, stop!
You can't go to him!
Don't you want to go home?!
Don't touch me!
Cockroach!
Get away from me, cockroach!
Nami, are you alright?!
Y-Yeah.
Don't get cocky, you bastard!
No, Usopp!
Let go of me! We've got to use force to stop them. It's the only way!
They're hallucinating! He just called you a cockroach!
But...
these children are victims!
They haven't done anything wrong!
Take these chains off me!
It hurts!
But if we don't do something...
these kids will kill us!
Then direct that anger...
at him!
Take them off!
Take these chains off me!
You've got to be kidding!
They broke their chains?!
Magnificent! How strong you have become!
That little...
Candy.
Master.
Please...
Just you wait, damn gas bastard!
The most effective thing against gas would be...
Deadly...
Fire Bird Star!
Stay back, kids!
Were you expecting me to explode?
So you know that I have gas powers.
But you see,
I can extinguish fire before it touches me!
Poison gas isn't the only kind of gas there is.
Air itself is a gas as well.
So that means that I can control the air around me.
Remove the oxygen and all flame dies out...
and you become unable to breathe!
Like so!
Usopp!
Black Ball...
Thundercloud...
Master.
C-Candy.
Candy.
Did I hear you say that
you think Straw Hat missed me?
As a matter of fact, we did meet!
I suffocated him and the other two!
Candy!
Now!
Master!
Gimme! Gimme!
Children. Only good kids
who return to the laboratory get candy.
We'll be good! We'll be good kids!
Then you can be patient for a little longer, can you not?
Very well, but first...
these demons took you away
and made your disease worse.
Exterminate them!
Take those big pipes...
and smash their heads in!
Yes.
Stop... it.
Head... spinning...
Caesar!
Brownie!
His name is Brownbeard!
Straw Hat Pirates!
I see now!
Who are you again?
Oh, I remember!
My powerful subordinate, Brownbeard!
Did you forget that I even existed?!
Of course not!
What happened to you?
It looks like you were badly burned. It's painful just to look at you.
You were the one who ordered them to do this to me!
Brownbeard?
You're on the hit list as well.
He's an idiot so he's easy to use,
but he has become a burden.
We don't need him anymore.
Kill him.
The Cool Brothers, am I right?
So that's why you were burned!
I trusted you!
You shouldn't be so upset.
You survived an attack from the Cool Brothers.
You're quite lucky, really!
Silence!
Caesar!
Children! It's dangerous here!
Get aboard the gas balloon outside!
Let's get away from this place!
Wait! Don't go with him!
Caesar!
The fact that you deceived me doesn't really matter.
I... don't care.
But you will return my crew to me!
I will not let them suffer the same fate that I did!
Imbecile! You have no crew!
All of them, including you,
belong to me now, remember?
How long are you gonna keep pretending that you're a captain?
You're the most pathetic pirate scum
in the New World!
Hey, Nami! We've gotta chase after the kids.
Yes.
They will continue to obey me,
believing that I am their god of salvation!
They're just too stupid to realize...
that they're merely being kept alive
so I can use them as human guinea pigs!
You filth!
Gastanet.
Brownbeard?!
What happened?!
Gastanet!
Master.
Hey, where did Master go?
Caesar speaking.
I have successfully retrieved the children.
Has Smiley's food been prepared?
All the preparations you ordered us to perform have been carried out, Master.
and the Surveillance Snails are outside, ready to go.
So we can begin the live broadcast
of our fun experiment as soon as Smiley arrives?
Indeed.
Good. Connect me to all receivers.
Understood.
Distinguished underworld brokers from all over the world...
Pardon the abruptness of this experiment,
but you are lucky to get to see this.
The gas weapon I am about to show you...
is even more effective
than the one from four years ago,
and it's an item that the trash
from the World Government could never produce.
Uninvited guests
wandered onto my island earlier today...
and I will be performing this experiment on them.
Conquest. War. Dominion.
This weapon has many possible uses.
If it is to your liking, shall we make a deal?
Are you interested
in this weapon of mass destruction?
Nah.
But... it can't hurt to see it in action.